https://www.eriezoo.org/privacy-policy

BUY MEMBERSHIP
BUY TICKETS
BUY CLASSES
VisitRates, Hours & DirectionsMembershipAnimal CamsGroupsAnimalsGardensAmenitiesRidesShoppingFoodOtherZoo FAQNewsAnnouncementsSupportWays to HelpVolunteerCapital CampaignAnimal SponsorshipsPlanned GivingEnrichment Wish ListEmergency FundGift ShopEducationEducation ClassesScout GroupsToursClassroom PresentationsSchool Groups / Spring Field TripsJunior ZooKeeperSummer CampsTraveling ZooEventsUpcoming EventsBirthday PartiesIce CenterAboutLearn to SkateContactDonation RequestsContact
VisitOverviewRates, Hours & DirectionsMembershipAnimal CamsGroupsAnimalsGardensAmenitiesRidesShoppingFoodOtherZoo FAQNewsAnnouncementsSupportWays to HelpVolunteerCapital CampaignAnimal SponsorshipsPlanned GivingEnrichment Wish ListEmergency FundGift ShopEducationEducation ClassesScout GroupsToursClassroom PresentationsSchool Groups / Spring Field TripsJunior ZooKeeperSummer CampsTraveling ZooEventsUpcoming EventsBirthday PartiesIce CenterAboutLearn to SkateContactDonation RequestsContact
Privacy Policy
Home
Visit Overview Rates, Hours & Directions Membership Animal Cams Groups Animals Gardens Amenities Rides Shopping Food Other Zoo FAQ News Announcements Support Ways to Help Volunteer Capital Campaign Animal Sponsorships Planned Giving Enrichment Wish List Emergency Fund Gift Shop Education Education Classes Scout Groups Tours Classroom Presentations School Groups / Spring Field Trips Junior ZooKeeper Summer Camps Traveling Zoo Events Upcoming Events Birthday Parties Ice Center About Learn to Skate Contact Donation Requests Contact
Web Site Privacy Policy
The Erie Zoo is committed to protecting the privacy of its online guests, customers, members, and patrons. This privacy policy applies to transactions made, and data gathered, on the Erie Zoo web sites. By using the Zoo web sites or communicating with the Zoo by email, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Privacy Policy
The Erie Zoo web site offers broad public access to and use of a wide range of information comprised of data, images, and text files to visitors of all ages. We are dedicated to safeguarding all information collected online.
To help ensure a rewarding online experience for all visitors, the Zoo provides this summary of our information practices. This privacy notice governs the collection and use of information on our web sites.
As the zoo continues to offer our visitors new and different types of content and services, we may modify our practices from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information collected in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time the information is collected.
Information We Collect
When you order from the Erie Zoo, we collect your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, and credit card number, including expiration date and v-code. We also gather information on the person who will receive any gift you send (e.g., that person's name and address) and we will retain a record of your purchases.
How We Use the Information
The Erie Zoo uses visitor's personal information for internal purposes only. We may also use personal information provided by shoppers to send them, by email or direct mail, notification of special offers or sale events. We may also use your contact information to notify you about upcoming events and or exhibitions. If you do not want to receive information, you will have the opportunity to opt out.
We never sell, rent, or otherwise share our visitor's personal information with third parties. We will disclose information we maintain as required by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a specific law enforcement agency's request.
Return policy:
No refunds on tickets purchasedEdZoocation classes are very popular and fill quickly. A limited number of seats are class. Therefore, there is a $2 fee for each cancellation. If you cancel less than 7 dayscheduled class, there is no refund. Questions about a transaction? Call Kelly at the Zoo at 814-864-4091 extension 272.
Security Policy:
Because your credit card security is a high priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure your payment information is processed confidentially, accurately, and securely. Our site uses encryption technology, such as Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), to protect your credit card information during data transport. SSL encrypts ordering information such as your name, physical address, and credit card number.
In order to process a return from your credit card please call the Zoo at 814-864-4091.
To provide you with an increased level of security online, when you register for an online account you also select a password to access your personal information. The Erie Zoo will not ask you for your password in an unsolicited communication.
Contact Us
If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at the following email address, mailing address and telephone
info@eriezoo.orgContact the Erie Zoo Office directly: (814)-864-4091 423 W. 38th St. Erie, PA 16508
